Guys, guys, I've
got great news.
Guess what.
Uh... Monica's pregnant.
Really?
Let's get past the moment.
What-what's your news?
Thank you.
I got a job in advertising.
Hey!
Honey, that's incredible!
Gosh, what's
the pay like?
Oh, come on, people.
Come on now.
If I don't know
who makes the most,
how do I know who
I like the most?
Hi, Joey.
Well, actually it pays nothing.
It's an internship.
Oh, that's cool. We have interns
at Days of Our Lives.
Right, so it'll be the same,
except less sex with you.
ROSS:
So, uh, what
kind of stuff
do you think
they'll have you do there?
Well, it's a training program,
but at the end,
they hire the people they like.
That's great.
Yeah, I mean, there's probably
going to be some gruntwork,
which will probably stink.
You know, a grown man
getting people coffee
is a little humiliating.
Humiliating and noble.
Thank you.
You know, if-if I didn't
already have a job,
I think I would have been
really good in advertising.
Ross, you did not come up
with "Got Milk?"
Yes, I did! I did!
I should have written it down.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always stuck
in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
( knocking )
Hey.
Where's Chandler?
I want to wish him good luck
on his first day.
And I smelled bacon. Ha-ha.
He just left.
Who did?
Joey, you're never going
to believe it.
She called.
She did?
You got it!
I did?!
What is she talking about?
I don't know, but
it sounds great!
No, your agent called.
You got that audition!
With Leonard Hayes?
Yes!
Oh, my God,
that is great!
That is great.
It's for a play on Broadway.
And in a real theater.
Not that little one
underneath the deli
like last time.
Is it a good play?
Well, it must be,
because I read it,
and I didn't understand
a single word!
And Leonard Hayes
is starring in it.
Yeah, yeah,
and directing.
Oh, he was so good in that movie
of Macbeth.
You saw that?
No, but I saw the previews.
They played it
right before Jackass.
Oh.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He has. Yeah, he's
done some amazing work.
Oh, yeah. Oh, I loved him
in those cell phone commercials.
I know. When the
monkey hits him
in the face with
giant rubber phone.
Hey, maybe the monkey will be
at the audition.
Don't make me more nervous
than I already am.
Good morning, everybody.
Can I get you a
cup of coffee, sir?
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm an intern,
just like you guys,
except for the tie,
the briefcase, and...
the fact that I can rent a car.
Seriously,
you're an intern?
Yeah, well, I'm kind of heading
in a new career direction,
and, you know,
you got to start
at the bottom.
Dude.
All right, look, I know
I'm a little bit older
than you guys,
but it's not like I'm Bob Hope.
The comedian?
USO?
Uh, it's USA, sir.
This is Joey Tribbiani.
Joey, these are the producers,
and as you probably
already know,
this is Leonard Hayes.
Hi.
Wow.
It is so amazing to meet you.
I am such a big fan
of your work.
Well, I've, uh,
I've been blessed
with, uh, a lot of...
a lot of great roles.
Oh, tell me about it, huh.
Unlimited nights and weekends.
Are you making fun of me?
Because I am
not a sellout.
I didn't do that for the money.
I believe in those phones.
I almost lost a cousin
because of bad wireless service.
No, no. I-I wasn't making fun
of you, honestly.
I-I think you were great
in those commercials.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, I do
bring a certain credibility
to the role.
It's true.
Are you kidding?
When they shoot you
out of that cannon...
Hang up that phone.
One take.
Wow.
We did that
in one take.
So, shall we, uh, read?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Top of act two.
This is my entrance.
You got it?
Mm-hmm.
What the hell are
you still doing here?
Ooh!
Uh...
I think you know.
Bastard!
I am what you made me.
You know what?
I could go right now.
Go, go.
I can't.
Oh, I want to, Long Pause.
But I can't.
I'm so sorry.
You-you... you're not
supposed to say "Long Pause."
Oh.
Oh, I thought
that was your character's name.
You know?
I thought you were, like,
an Indian or something.
You know with the...
Sorry.
Long Pause. No.
Thank you so much
for coming in.
We appreciate it.
Thank you.
Well, are you sure
you don't want me
to do it again?
I could do it...
with an accent?
You know, Southern.
( Jamaican accent ):
I could go right now, mon.
Huh?
My God in heaven.
Joey, hang on for a second.
Leonard, can we talk
to you for a moment?
Yes.
Listen, I'm going
to bring him back.
You... you've got
to be kidding.
He-he can't act.
I can work
with him and...
Hey, I-I don't care
if you think he's hot.
You know, if you want
to sleep with him,
do it on your own time.
This is a play.
Leonard, I'm
bringing him back.
No, listen.
If you insist on this,
I will call my agent
so fast on a cell phone
that has a connection
that is so clear,
he's going to think
I'm next door.
Uh, hi. Uh...
thank you so much
for whispering for my benefit,
but, um, look.
If you just tell me
what I did wrong,
I would love to work on it
and come back
and try it again for you.
And-and, also, how you doin'?
( laughs )
If you please, just-just
give me another chance.
I really want to get better.
Please.
Well... well,
if you want to come back
at the end of the day today,
here are my
notes. Ready?
Yeah, yeah.
Um, you're in your head.
You're-you're thinking
way too much.
I really doubt that.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's that... it's that
you're not connected
with anything
in your body.
There's no urgency.
The scene
is a struggle.
Uh-huh.
It's a...
it's a race.
Uh-huh.
Also, what you did
was horizontal.
Don't be afraid
to explore...
the vertical,
you know?
Uh-huh.
And don't learn
the words.
Let the words learn you.
Couldn't I just sleep
with the producer?
Hey, do you want
to go to dinner tonight?
Oh, I can't.
I've-I've got a date with
that waitress, uh, Katie.
Yeah. I-I know
we've only gone
out, like, twice,
but I don't know.
I have a really good
feeling about her.
Oh, I hear divorce bells.
Uh.
All right, just
give me your wallets,
and there won't be a problem.
What?
I have a gun.
Okay, just-just
relax, Phoebe.
Just stay calm.
Oh, my God, I can't
find my wallet!
All right, lady,
now give me your purse.
No.
What do you mean, no?
I knew you'd be my
death, Phoebe Buffay!
Lowell, is that you?
Phoebe?
Oh, my God!
Unbelievable.
Oh, my God.
Oh. Well, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
Ross, this is my old friend
Lowell from the streets.
( laughs )
Lowell, Ross.
Ross, nice to meet you.
Yeah, a real pleasure.
Oh. It's been so long.
Oh, so long.
I can't believe you're
still doing this.
Uh, I know...
but I quit smoking.
Good for you.
So, you look
like you're doing
really well.
I guess your mugging days
are behind you.
Oh.
Oh, my God!
Phoebe, you used to mug people?
Excuse me, Ross.
Old friends
catching up.
( laughing )
Hey.
Hey. How did the audition go?
Well, they want
to see me again this afternoon,
but, uh, boy, Leonard Hayes
did not like me.
What happened?
Uh, he said I wasn't urgent
enough, you know,
and that everything I did
was horizontal,
and I should be more vertical.
Oh, and he said
that I should think less.
Well, so far, so good.
Honey, I'm old.
What's wrong?
I am so much older
than other these interns.
I can't compete with them.
So, you're a
little older.
Try to look at
the positive.
You have all this
life experience.
Yes, but I don't think
life experience
is going to help me...
with these.
Wow!
It's like they're on fire.
What are they?
They're these
prototype sneakers,
and I have to come up with ideas
on how to sell them,
which I can't do,
because no self-respecting adult
would ever wear these.
I'll give you $500 for them.
What am I supposed
to do with these?
All right, come on.
Sneakers are easy.
You wear sneakers all the time.
Well, first of all,
they're not called sneakers
anymore.
Apparently, they're called
"kicks" or "skids."
And I think heard somebody say
"slorps."
Here, look.
They got these wheels
that pop out from the bottom
so you can roll around,
because, apparently,
walking is too much exercise.
Kids, kids, roll your way
to childhood obesity.
Would you help me
try to sell these?
Okay, have you considered
using a girl with huge knockers?
I-I don't think that's the kind
of thing they're looking for.
Hey, that'd work on me.
Why do you think
I buy Mrs. Butterworth's?
Hey.
Hey, you'll never guess
what just happened.
( groans )
Phoebe and I
got mugged!
Are you okay?
Yeah, because Phoebe
knew the mugger.
How do you know a mugger?
I'm sorry I have friends
outside the six of us.
You want to know
how she knew him?
Because Phoebe
used to mug people.
Seriously?
Well, I'm not proud of it.
But, you know, sometimes,
when I was living on the street
and I needed money for food
and stuff, I...
Phoebe, that is awful.
Well, okay, I wasn't rich
like you guys, okay?
I didn't eat gold
and have a flying pony.
I had a hard life.
My mother was killed
by a drug dealer.
Your mother killed herself.
She was a drug dealer!
Well, anyway, it was
a good thing Phoebe knew him
because I was about to do
some serious damage.
( chuckling ):
Okay.
Wow, this must have brought back
some really bad memories
for you, Ross.
Why?
Well, Ross was mugged as a kid.
You were?
Yeah.
And it was pretty traumatic.
It was outside
St. Mark's Comics.
You know, I was just there
minding my own business,
you know, seeing what kind
of trouble
Spider-Man got into that week.
( coughing ):
Wonder Woman.
Anyway, I was heading towards
this bakery, you know,
to pick up a couple of dozen
Linzertortes for someone.
When out of nowhere, this-this
thug with a pipe jumps out
and says,
"Give me your money, punk!"
Oh, my God.
I know.
Yeah, and the worst part was
they took my backpack
which had all the original
artwork I had done
for my own comic book,
Science Boy.
Oh, yeah.
What was his superpower again?
A superhuman thirst
for knowledge.
I-I better get to class.
Are there any more
of your friends
I should look out for
on my way, Phoebe?
No. Actually, you might want
to stay away from Jane Street.
That's where Stabby Joe works.
Okay, I think we
have a problem here.
What?
Well, um, back in my
mugging days, you know,
I, um, I worked
St. Mark's Comics.
Yeah?
Well, a pipe was
my weapon of choice.
And, um, preteen comic
book nerds were my meat.
So?
Well, there was
this one kid
who had a sticker on
his backpack that said,
"Geology rocks."
Oh, my God.
I know! I mugged Ross!
You're late.
I know, I'm sorry.
But can I just have
a quick second
to run to the bathroom?
No. Leonard doesn't wait.
But I am bursting with Yoo-hoo.
Joey, here we go.
Let's go, very quickly.
Actually, I really need...
We must go now, quickly, please.
Okay, yes, sir.
Aah...
Ready?
What the hell are you
still doing here?
I think you know.
Oh, you sick bastard.
I am what you made me.
You know what?
What?
I could go right now.
Then go, go.
Oh, I-I can't.
I want to, but I can't.
Cut.
That was good.
That was very good.
You did everything
I asked for.
I did?
Yes, plus, what,
you've got this,
I don't know
what you got going--
this squirmy quality
Well, I...
that you're bringing
to the character
that I couldn't
have even imagined.
Wow. Hey, here's what
we're going to do.
Come back tomorrow
for the final call-backs
with the backers,
do all of this--
what you got going now--
but you know what? More. More.
Can you do that?
Sure, yeah.
I-I don't have time
to say thank you
because I really got to go.
Look at that.
Still in character.
I like it.
I plant seeds...
I can't explain it.
I don't know.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Putting on
the sneakers.
Thought I'd get
in the younger mindset.
You know,
see if it sparked anything.
Oh, anything yet?
Yes, how's this?
"They're so uncomfortable,
it's like getting kicked
in the nuts for your feet."
Hey.
Hi.
( humming )
( rummaging )
Probably wondering
what I'm doing.
No, that seems about right.
Yesterday, at my audition,
I really had to pee
and apparently, having to pee
makes me a really good actor.
I got a call-back,
so I'm drinking everything.
Oh, hey, by the way.
Mm-hmm.
That eggnog in our fridge
was great.
Joey, that was formula.
We got to get more of that.
You know what,
these aren't half bad.
You should suggest
something like these
to Ralph Lauren.
Okay, first of all,
that's stupid.
And second of all, I'm not
allowed to talk to Ralph.
All right.
I feel younger already.
Yeah, I think
I broke my hip.
Hey, you.
Hey.
How was class?
No one ever asks me that.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I really want to know.
Oh, uh...
Well, um, it was actually
a rather lively discussion
about the Pleistocene...
All right,
nothing is worth this.
Um, I have a...
I have a confession to make.
Um, okay, you know that, um,
that girl that mugged you
when you were a kid?
What-what are you
talking about?
It wasn't a girl.
It was this-this huge dude.
You don't have
to lie anymore, Ross.
I know that it was
a 14-year-old girl.
No, it wasn't.
Yes, it was!
No, it wasn't!
You don't think I would have
defended myself
against a 14-year-old...
Give your money, punk.
Oh, my God, it was you!
I can't believe it.
You... you mugged me?!
Yeah.
And I'm so, so sorry, Ross.
I'm sorry.
But, you know, if you think
about it, it's kind of neat.
I mean,
well, it-it's just that
I've always felt
kind of like an outsider.
You know, the rest of you
have these connections
that go way back.
And, you know, now you and I
have... have a great one.
It's not the best.
I know. I'm s...
Please, forgive me.
I don't know what to say.
There's nothing you can say.
That was the most humiliating
thing that ever happened to me.
Really?
Even more humiliating than...?
Let's not do this.
...and then, at the
end of the commercial,
the girls get out
of the hot tub,
start making out
with each other.
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
That's interesting.
Just one thought.
You didn't mention the shoes.
Who's next?
Chandler.
Okay. You start on the image
of a guy putting on the shoes.
He's about my age.
( scoffs ):
Your age?
Uh-huh!
So, he's rolling
down the street
and he starts to lose control.
You know, maybe he falls.
Maybe he hurts himself.
Just then, a kid comes flying by
wearing the shoes.
He jumps over the old guy
and laughs.
And the line reads,
"Not suitable for adults."
Chandler, that's great.
Ah, thank you, sir.
Or
man-who's-two-years-younger-
than-me.
You see, that has
a clear selling point.
It appeals to our
key demographic.
How did you come up with that?
I don't know, I don't know,
I don't know!
I was just... I tried
to get in the young mindset
and, you know,
stuff started to flow.
Well, that is great.
Good work.
Thank you.
We'll see all of you
tomorrow.
Okay.
The cold weather hurts my hip.
Hey, Ross.
Okay, look,
I know you're still
mad at me
but can I just talk to you
for a sec?
Sure, go ahead.
Oh, sorry.
I just really wanted
to apologize again.
And-and also show you something
I think you'll find
very exciting.
Oh, my God!
"Crap from the street"!
Look, Ross, in this box are all
the things I got from mugging
that I thought were too special
to sell... or smoke.
Anyway, I was looking through it
and I found...
Science Boy.
( quietly ):
Oh, my God.
I never thought
I'd see this again.
What...? Uh...
It's all here.
Oh, I-I...
Wha...?
What made you save it
all these years?
I guess I just thought
it was really good.
And-and maybe it would be worth
something one day.
You really thought Science Boy
was worth saving?
Well, yeah.
But you should know,
I also have a jar of Vaseline
and a cat skull in here.
Still, this-this is amazing.
Oh, my God.
Thank you, Phoebe.
Oh, you're welcome.
And thank you, for Science Boy.
I learned a lot from him.
You're welcome.
I need an answer!
I-I can't tell you
something I don't know.
You know!
I don't know.
I need an answer, now!
All right, all right.
Here, you want an answer?
The answer is...
Oh...!
She never loved me.
She only loved you.
You knew this all along
and you never told me?
You never told me?
I can never forgive you.
I can never forgive myself.
I have nothing to live for.
Bang, end scene.
( breathing deeply )
Absolutely amazing.
The part is yours.
Oh, thanks.
Thanks. Now I really
have to get going...
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Congratulations.
You did it. You did it.
Oh, you can relax now.
Yeah.
( sighing with relief )
Huh. You don't have a job,
but you have no problem
ordering porn.
On a Saturday afternoon?
I was in the house.
Hey, uh, Phoebe didn't
by any chance mention that...?
She was the huge guy
that mugged you? Yeah.
I see.
You didn't happen to tell...?
Everybody we know? Yeah.
Great. Thanks.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org